## YOSEFI KROYTORO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, SOFTWARE ANALYST

#### ∘ DETAILS ∘

Tel Aviv

**\** 054-7556216

Sefi0609@gmail.com

#### • LINKS •

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

#### SKILLS

Python

Java

C/C++

QA

**AWS** 

WAF

HTML

SQLite

MySQL

Streamlit

Django

GitHub

Git

JavaFX

Scene Builder PyCharm

Visual Studio

Active Directory
IntelliJ IDEA

Linux

Windows

Microsoft office

#### **PROFILE**

BSc in Computer Science, Cyber Security Program, The Open University.

High self-learning ability, excellent functioning in a stressful and multi-tasking environment.

Technical understanding, ability to work alone and in a team, excellent interpersonal skills.

Experience in solving complex technical problems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2021 — Present: NOC at Coolvision, Tel Aviv

#### Developing online video streaming platforms, used by millions of users across the globe

- Working with diversified and advance tools to monitor performance and capability of the company systems. Collecting and analyzing data
  - Monitoring of cybersecurity incidents and providing an initial response
    - Working to triage and troubleshooting production issues
    - Performing usability and quality tests on the company's systems
  - Providing solutions to user's login faults, working with customer service staff

# 2021: Technical Support at Ness Technologies, Tel Aviv One of the leading, oldest and largest information technology services in Israel

- Support for real-time softwares, systems and platforms
  - User management, setting up new users
- Run tests for software and system integrity on users' computers
- Working with remote control softwares, user management software, medical systems and servers

2018-2021: Manufacturing Specialist at intel, Qiryat Gat Multinational corporation, the world's largest semiconductor chip manufacturer

Production line expert

### **PROJECTS**

#### **Portfolio Website**

In this website you will find full-stack projects, websites and desktop applications I've built using Python, C++ and Java. In these projects I've used APIs, Sockets, Threads, Git, GitHub, MySQL, SQLite, Encryptions, Web Frameworks and GUIs. All in one accessible website - Link

#### **MILITARY SERVICE**

2014-2017: Aircraft Technician Team Leader, Air Force of Israel

#### **EDUCATION**

2020-2024: BSc in Computer Science, Cyber Security Program, GPA: 82, The Open University 2012-2014: Electronics and Computers Practical Engineer, Haifa Air Force Technological College

#### ○ LANGUAGES ○

English – Fluent

Hebrew - Native